Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1975; F-20-3; 44 cm of textual records
  - Faculty dispute, 1967 - 1975; F-20-3-4; 31 cm of textual records
    - Faculty dispute - news releases, 1968 - 1971; F-20-3-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - presidential news releases, 1969 - 1971; F-20-3-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute - court depositions, 1969 - 1970; F-20-3-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute - injunctions, 1969 - 1970; F-20-3-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute - Friends of the Learned Societies, 1970 - 1971; F-20-3-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute, 1967 - 1969; F-20-3-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute, 1970 - 1971; F-20-3-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Faculty dispute, 1972; F-20-3-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
- Departmental committees, 1965 - 1974; F-20-4; 64 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records of various departmental committees. It includes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and memoranda.
  Access to records in the subseries "Appointments," "Chairman's search," "Grievance", and "Salaries and Promotions" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Departmental committees, 1968 - 1973; F-20-4-1; 2 cm of textual records
    - Faculty committee membership, 1968 - 1969; F-20-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Committees, 1969 - 1971; F-20-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Committees, 1971 - 1973; F-20-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
  - Appointments committee, 1968 - 1974; F-20-4-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Appointments committee, 1968 - 1970; F-20-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-20-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
  - Budget committee, 1966 - 1969; F-20-4-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Budget committee, 1966 - 1969; F-20-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-15)
  - Chairman's search committee, 1971 - 1972; F-20-4-4; 4 cm of textual records
    - Chairman's search committee, 1971 - 1972; F-20-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Chairman's search committee, 1972; F-20-4-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Chairman's search committee, 1972; F-20-4-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - O'Neil, 1972; F-20-4-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
  - Curriculum committee, 1967 - 1970; F-20-4-5; 3 cm of textual records
    - Curriculum committee, 1967 - 1968; F-20-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Curriculum committee, 1969; F-20-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Curriculum committee, 1969 - 1970; F-20-4-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
  - Department meetings, 1965 - 1974; F-20-4-6; 30 cm of textual records
    - Departmental meetings, 1965; F-20-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Departmental meetings, 1965; F-20-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-20-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-20-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-16)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-20-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1966; F-20-4-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-20-4-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-20-4-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-20-4-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1967; F-20-4-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-20-4-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
      Restricted in whole
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-20-4-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-20-4-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 20-17)
    - Departmental meetings, 1968; F-20-4-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-20-4-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-20-4-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-20-4-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1969; F-20-4-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1970; F-20-4-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1971; F-20-4-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1972; F-20-4-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1973 - 1974; F-20-4-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 20-18)
  - Executive committee, 1969 - 1974; F-20-4-7; 3 cm of textual records
    - Executive committee, 1969 - 1970; F-20-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Executive committee, 1971; F-20-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Executive committee, 1972 - 1974; F-20-4-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
  - Graduate studies committee, 1966 - 1974; F-20-4-8; 16 cm of textual records
    - Graduate studies committee, 1966 - 1969; F-20-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1969; F-20-4-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1970; F-20-4-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1971; F-20-4-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972 - 1974; F-20-4-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-4-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-4-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-4-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-19)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-4-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-4-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
      Restricted in Whole
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-4-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-4-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-20-4-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-4-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-4-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-20-4-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    - Registrar's office, 1967 - 1972; F-20-4-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
  - Grievance committee, 1968 - 1971; F-20-4-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Grievance committee, 1968 - 1971; F-20-4-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
  - Majors and honours committee, 1967; F-20-4-10; 1 cm of textual records
    - Major and honors committee, 1967; F-20-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
  - Salaries and promotions committee, 1967 - 1970; F-20-4-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Salaries and promotions committee, 1967 - 1970; F-20-4-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
- University committees, 1966 - 1973; F-20-5; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records relating to the Faculty Committee on University Development and a Senate paper on the splitting of the Department. It includes correspondence and memoranda.
  - Faculty committee on university development, 1966 - 1967; F-20-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
    Open
  - Senate paper on PSA Split I, 1973; F-20-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
  - Senate paper on PSA Split II, 1973; F-20-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-20)
  - Senate paper on PSA Split III, 1973; F-20-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Senate paper on PSA Split IV, 1973; F-20-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Senate paper on PSA Split V, 1973; F-20-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
- Departmental reviews, 1969; F-20-6; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of materials relating to the External Review committee charged with evaluating the external review of the Department in 1969. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - PSA review, 1969; F-20-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
- Course outlines, 1965 - 1973; F-20-7; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of undergraduate course outlines and booklets.
  - PSA courses - general, 1968 - 1972; F-20-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course outlines, 1965 - 1967; F-20-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course outlines, 1968; F-20-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course outlines, 1969; F-20-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course outlines, 1969; F-20-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course outlines, 1970; F-20-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Courses - directed readings, 1971; F-20-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - Course booklets, 1972 - 1973; F-20-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
  - PSA 474 refusal, 1969; F-20-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-21)
- Archaeological Sites Advisory Board, 1967 - 1970; F-20-8; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Archaeological Sites Advisory Board. It includes draft budgets, correspondence, map copies, and memoranda.
  - Archaeological Sites Advisory Board, 1967 - 1970; F-20-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-21)